<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on Rebel Shrug</title>
    <link>https://rebelshrug.github.io/categories/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on Rebel Shrug</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 09:30:42 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rebelshrug.github.io/categories/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>pirate ipsum</title>
      <link>https://rebelshrug.github.io/post/pirate-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 09:30:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rebelshrug.github.io/post/pirate-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Follow my blog with Bloglovin
Prow scuttle parrel provost Sail ho shrouds spirits boom mizzenmast yardarm. Pinnace holystone mizzenmast quarter crow&amp;rsquo;s nest nipperkin grog yardarm hempen halter furl. Swab barque interloper chantey doubloon starboard grog black jack gangway rutters.
Deadlights jack lad schooner scallywag dance the hempen jig carouser broadside cable strike colors. Bring a spring upon her cable holystone blow the man down spanker Shiver me timbers to go on account lookout wherry doubloon chase.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>bacon ipsum</title>
      <link>https://rebelshrug.github.io/post/bacon-ipsum/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 14:48:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rebelshrug.github.io/post/bacon-ipsum/</guid>
      <description>Spicy jalapeno bacon ipsum dolor amet short loin exercitation anim dolore kielbasa. Nisi turkey consequat incididunt andouille turducken t-bone. Officia incididunt consequat, non swine culpa ut. Beef laboris aute, et venison ad corned beef. Rump prosciutto reprehenderit cillum shoulder leberkas culpa id, sirloin incididunt nostrud consequat.
Venison reprehenderit exercitation, voluptate labore culpa beef rump ball tip pariatur officia shoulder aute. Pork belly culpa doner nulla drumstick short loin. Rump id tempor drumstick picanha excepteur.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>